{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"d7bce809-9016-4311-be98-aba3c1f2d0a1"},"exam":{"id":"d80f2d0f-feca-42ec-9ff7-9493ce03182f","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"c314b972-e56b-46d5-a876-4754ac7a336a","domain":"tech","question":"A Web Application Firewall operates at which layer of the OSI model?","explanation":"The seven layers of the OSI model in ascending order are Physical, Data, Network, Transport, Session, Presentation, Application. A Web Application Firewall protects web traffic from mallicious exploits and operates at the Application layer, Layer 7. Network-level protection, like that offered by AWS Shield, operates at Layer 4.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/waf/","title":"AWS WAF"}],"answers":[{"id":"73d19b475178ae97c94ed26431e3b138","text":"Layer 4","correct":false},{"id":"537c230a6d35c80a253f85b1c6d607c4","text":"Layer 7","correct":true},{"id":"0d5a8f512ae075b876e8bb239d6be642","text":"Layer 2","correct":false},{"id":"5ab5764b458bd4674dffe82c5f1cda53","text":"Layer 1","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true},{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true}]},{"id":"7e71f634-1fe3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Redshift?","explanation":"Amazon Redshift is AWSâ€™s data warehouse service designed to scale up to petabytes of structured data. Using Redshift, you can create a data warehouse with a set of nodes, which is referred to as a 'cluster'.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon Redshift?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c195feba1b6755cf70b23e85f649bea5","text":"It stores unstructured data.","correct":false},{"id":"cb8783f4a61d2d6ce45ab561107c68fe","text":"It is used to launch a set of nodes called a Redshift cluster.","correct":true},{"id":"1be4b9169c53e2842d313aa2e9fe2bc5","text":"It is a data warehouse service.","correct":true},{"id":"eae61ac52e73cabeaa3d471e1f2214dd","text":"It is designed for storing petabytes of data.","correct":true}]},{"id":"4uvrqex2-fb79-fccq-6ogx-umyvygaxn7fi","domain":"security","question":"You are using your corporate directory to grant your users access to AWS services. What is this called?","explanation":"Federated Access is when you use an external directory, such as your coroporate one, to grant users in that directory access to AWS resources. Role-based and User group are more used to definied which resources a user is able to access once they have access, not the method by which they gain that access. Multifactor Authentication Access is the concept of a user requiring 2 secrets to be able to access the resources - usually their password and a 1 time code provided by a device under their control (e.g. a mobile phone).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/identity/federation/","title":"Identity Federation"}],"answers":[{"id":"d3973accf5dd88240811572d5f2608eb","text":"Multifactor Authentication Access","correct":false},{"id":"00347e1d2de42be9910e334d04fe60dc","text":"Federated Access","correct":true},{"id":"0db642c28b60c6a51547c3da2262902b","text":"User Group Access","correct":false},{"id":"acce53b09f08060687cd88c30bce9db8","text":"Role-based Access","correct":false}]},{"id":"og6hjhzz-5hd0-yz2y-lhcp-id573kosdzz0","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authentication\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authentication is the first part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":true}]},{"id":"tcm0xjs5-ewk2-r9gc-kxjj-xzq1jdown7vb","domain":"tech","question":"AWS VPC is a component of which of the following overall services categories?","explanation":"VPC is a core component of AWS' network services and is the underlying resrource that allows your other resources and instances to communicate with each other privately.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"About VPC"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"Check it in the console"}],"answers":[{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"0ee907d052171640981d84888edab1da","text":"Migration Services","correct":false},{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":false},{"id":"57c28ff1fb9ea9b16bc846660a260623","text":"Networking and Content Delivery","correct":true},{"id":"897489f143e2ade13f1fadcd00d4cc7b","text":"Management Tools","correct":false},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false}]},{"id":"922bcb30-a895-4a3f-bb49-94c90e34a5ed","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services can Amazon CloudWatch use as a target to deliver near real-time streams of system events that describe changes in AWS resources?","explanation":"EC2 instances, AWS Lambda functions, and Amazon SQS queues are a few of the AWS services that can be configured as targets for CloudWatch events.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/events/WhatIsCloudWatchEvents.html","title":"What Is Amazon Cloudwatch Events?"}],"answers":[{"id":"4fc99f94726d4b95eaa8250076dc8f6f","text":"AWS Lambda functions","correct":true},{"id":"f4fb4c65fcc06f70081c87f3a00cb3a3","text":"Redshift clusters","correct":false},{"id":"afe6e803ff73335b743f02267c6a3f17","text":"EC2 instances","correct":true},{"id":"e5c6ffd5e16261a07c150339d8a42610","text":"Amazon SQS queues","correct":true}]},{"id":"d4c61d1c-2ada-4bc2-9cf9-2546f8d62025","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are valid S3 bucket names?","explanation":"The 'January-2020-sales-numbers' is the only S3 bucket name that is not valid; bucket names must not contain uppercase letters, and they must start with a lowercase letter or number. The other three responses are valid, since they do not violate bucket naming rules.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev//BucketRestrictions.html#bucketnamingrules","title":"Rules for Bucket Naming"}],"answers":[{"id":"799de5bb8d3ce8dd91b7c8416efaa490","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/January-2020-sales-numbers","correct":false},{"id":"429e0b5ab4b0f9b9f14d8be62cecde68","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2020-january-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"9b55e7cfabcca3d69f5596c5122f46b2","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/january-2020-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"5843ebf1fe3709048eb1d4ca8bdc00aa","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/012020-sales-numbers","correct":true}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false}]},{"id":"fb40110c-2ee1-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can you use to analyze data?","explanation":"Amazon Kinesis is used to analyze data and video streams in real time, and QuickSight is used to analyze visualizations of customer data. So, both are classified as AWS analytics services. By contrast, Amazon Detective analyzes and visualizes security data, and AWS IAM enables the management of access to AWS services and resources securely. So, neither Detective nor IAM are analytics services; they actually fall under the Security, Identity, and Compliance category.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"1590671ce414a2deba7ba0a04fef39b3","text":"Amazon Kinesis","correct":true},{"id":"a86087964fb00f6ae81475d2c8c3c40c","text":"AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)","correct":false},{"id":"12fc352b40e25021e08572ca0f5d2b11","text":"Amazon Detective","correct":false},{"id":"c52be467fd0472e51b0f2acb2f234421","text":"Amazon QuickSight","correct":true}]},{"id":"3a04d665-f391-4b59-93bc-8e7e60565b99","domain":"tech","question":"Your project manager (PM) tasked you with launching an instance for a web application to be developed for an NGO. The PM is especially interested in using an AWS service that provides predicable monthly pricing, and he expects the instance to have the ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. What AWS service should you use to launch this instance?","explanation":"Although EC2 could have been the correct answer, two things are key here: Predicable monthly pricing and instance ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. Lightsail accomplishes that; EC2 is more suitable for consistently high CPU performance, and costs vary according to usage.","links":[{"url":"https://lightsail.aws.amazon.com/ls/docs/en_us/articles/amazon-lightsail-frequently-asked-questions-faq","title":"Frequently Asked Questions in Amazon Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"1dd30e8d60c2a200781dbcc9286f0919","text":"Elasticsearch Service","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false},{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"90df786a-99f7-45c0-b4ed-126bfc6c55de","domain":"concepts","question":"A mobile shopping list app needs to be able to add, delete, and update items on specific lists anytime a user desires. The backend for the app will run on Amazon EC2 instances with Auto Scaling to manage fluctuations in user demand. Many times, a user will perform maintenance on many list items in a single session. What design characteristic must be incorporated into the app for these requirements to be met?","explanation":"In order for horizontal scaling to be effective, you'll want to make sure the app doesn't store previous transaction or session information on specific EC2 instances. That way, any EC2 instance provisioned by Auto Scaling can process the request. Leveraging load balancing is also a good practice, but doesn't address the need for a stateless app. Session affinity goes the other direction, directing a load balancer to route transactions to a specific instance each time. Bootstrapping runs scripts each time an EC2 instance is provisioned.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud - AWS Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"712738cb3dbc4b4aeb218af7b44b731c","text":"Use bootstrapping on the EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"175dc87c438249634b2c6104864a2e6a","text":"Leverage load balancing to distribute transactions to multiple nodes","correct":false},{"id":"7f3d1559e229505103abfd9297d2249c","text":"Make sure the app doesnâ€™t need knowledge of previous transactions","correct":true},{"id":"3169165ef00c3474aa673628039e0dc1","text":"Implement session affinity","correct":false}]},{"id":"b6f1e02c-1a49-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS CloudTrail?","explanation":"CloudTrail is actually enabled automatically when you create an AWS account. The other three responses are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awscloudtrail/latest/userguide/how-cloudtrail-works.html","title":"How CloudTrail Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"d70f308061c9f3b0aef10fe5b3a954ab","text":"With CloudTrail, you can create a trail that either applies to one Region or to all Regions.","correct":true},{"id":"c4817f75e8865468e0d6688b3f7fa9ae","text":"CloudTrail delivers log files within 15 minutes of account activity.","correct":true},{"id":"98be3a0e01d49274c41618e1b43ff9c5","text":"When you create an AWS account, you will have to manually enable CloudTrail.","correct":false},{"id":"38105bf4ed77d230d01428de259f3ea0","text":"By default, CloudTrail event log files are encrypted using Amazon S3 server-side encryption.","correct":true}]},{"id":"wzp94cj7-nvoj-2owh-4pxj-hrbz8160358x","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are criteria affecting your billing for RDS?","explanation":"RDS runs on EC2 instances, so much like an EC2 instance, you are charged based on how long the RDS instances are running, how much storage they have provisioned, and the requests they're processing. Standard monitoring is included for free with RDS instances, although Enhanced Monitoring is available for more information. Data Transfer in to RDS, like most other AWS services, is free","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"f7f231f31a2c9b561fe0b7963e550e6a","text":"Data transfer in","correct":false},{"id":"c2b89d380496f89ae6f7baf5d69be55f","text":"Standard monitoring services","correct":false},{"id":"f7b3ef9e030e62319f8b3b42154eb67f","text":"Additional storage","correct":true},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"a2c4368093f9a13bd6548416cca5570c","text":"Running duration of the RDS instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false},{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true}]},{"id":"4kl8vift-ulhd-37ni-39eb-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below can you host on S3?","explanation":"S3 can be used to host simple static websites - other types that are dynamic or require code to run on the server side cannot be hosted on solely on S3","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/gsg/S3-gsg-CommonUseScenarios.html","title":"Use Cases - S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"0e40272fa3d5a16e33d87e3cbc4e1e47","text":"Dynamic websites","correct":false},{"id":"7a2b1017f16fb3e5ef49418e637aac95","text":"E-Commerce websites","correct":false},{"id":"70ebe1a12fc1b6b0489f44de54de9fc3","text":"Streaming websites","correct":false},{"id":"6c64eca998fc24821b4da679e88bb285","text":"Static websites","correct":true}]},{"id":"150e71c2-9b46-4a48-bed4-ef89f73570ae","domain":"tech","question":"Although you know that your Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes are designed to be highly reliable, you want to further mitigate the possibility of a failure. Which of the following should you do?","explanation":"Backup of the EBS volumes can be created by taking point-in-time snapshots. These components are stored in S3. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/EBSSnapshots.html","title":"Amazon EBS Snapshots"},{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-building-fault-tolerant-applications.pdf?did=wp_card&trk=wp_card","title":"Fault-Tolerant Components on AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"2f63e74501f200b9859c7b5976101e79","text":"Make copies of the EBS volumes and store them in Amazon S3.","correct":false},{"id":"a2a7a68497095df080fb01033b2aea46","text":"Create backups of the EBS volumes in Amazon RDS.","correct":false},{"id":"e2f843acc6781a153857118f92da89f4","text":"Mitigating the possibility of a failure is not necessary.","correct":false},{"id":"44023459578ef9dc57780fc55ee56f7d","text":"Take snapshots of the EBS volumes.","correct":true}]},{"id":"b04194cb-7c18-41fd-af07-af547fcdf3df","domain":"security","question":"A consulting firm is conducting a Sarbanes-Oxley compliance audit of your IT operations. The auditor requests visibility to logs of event history across your AWS-based employee expense system infrastructure. Which AWS service will record and provide give you the information you need?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail provides visibility to API call activity for AWS infrastructure and other services. AWS Cloudwatch Logs might be part of a centralized logging solution, but all API event information will come from CloudTrail. AWS Systems Manager can process EC2 logs only, and AWS Compliance Manager is not a service offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/?nc2=h_m1","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"811708e04896b95951b61e58635cc92d","text":"AWS Compliance Manager","correct":false},{"id":"28408acf54ab04fe847fd24957e528d9","text":"AWS CloudWatch Logs","correct":false}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true}]},{"id":"2cae08d8-1bce-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following types of data transfer concerning Amazon EC2 are free?","explanation":"All data transfer in to EC2 instances from the Internet is free. So is data transfer out of EC2 to CloudFront. Data transfer pricing out from EC2 to the Internet is free as long as it does not exceed 1 GB per month. Since this condition is not included in Response B, it isnâ€™t correct.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing â€“ Data Transfer"}],"answers":[{"id":"3b4e686ed0886b7be7e142139c38eb68","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to the Internet","correct":false},{"id":"9a1bfe89c1c91cf60b45ef77bf406e09","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to Amazon CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"2f08e8cef2078b8c6479a4b91faeeec3","text":"Data transfer in to EC2 from the Internet","correct":true},{"id":"279a4b71d3edd9b515bb71952e1a12c7","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to AWS GovCloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"1304f9de-9452-4311-84c4-d3a712c60203","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS Trusted Advisor best practice checks involves using Amazon CloudFront to accelerate data transfer from S3 buckets?","explanation":"By using Amazon CloudFront, requests for content in S3 buckets are automatically routed to the nearest edge location where content is cached. Consequently, data transfer is accelerated, ultimately improving performance.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":true},{"id":"fbb664cbac6d2822ec573a2477d39822","text":"Service Limits","correct":false},{"id":"d0bf6ab153eaa104c878925472ff129a","text":"Cost Optimization","correct":false}]},{"id":"48f2d351-b6b2-4615-a662-be8ca8a2b84f","domain":"tech","question":"Trusted Advisor is classified as what type of AWS service?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is a Management and Governance tool. It guides you on how to best manage your resources based on AWS best practices in five categories.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"458f5f8faf1e6121d97d167d4f94db24","text":"Management & Governance","correct":true},{"id":"5525aee13c9e8a25b1f35514f33ab825","text":"Security, Identity, and Compliance","correct":false},{"id":"c784a652acefe771f7a2853db61a07ae","text":"Application Integration","correct":false}]},{"id":"vikk5xb3-er5k-f530-xnql-upfbhr4zjhvv","domain":"concepts","question":"How many Availability Zones does each Region have?","explanation":"Normal Regions are made up of at least 2 Availability Zones to allow for highly available architectures in the cloud. The actual number of AZs can vary per Region.  There is a special class of Region called a 'Local Region' that have only 1 AZ, however that is viewed as an abnormal case by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"61f2018e5a51be7a751ae1eb61c1f017","text":"Regions don't have Availability Zones, Availability Zones have Regions","correct":false},{"id":"32cf9ef8a3f23b762138a410b9f02129","text":"Only 1","correct":false},{"id":"57ca7c66f61abc17eb42ff90f5bed87e","text":"At least 2","correct":true},{"id":"f3f74d2863be40169cddca9e902304f3","text":"At least 3","correct":false}]},{"id":"71sehgn8-lx4k-034j-srs9-vv6xhd7w10qh","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to performance efficiency?","explanation":"Of these choices, you should democratize advanced technologies, deploy into multiple Regions, and use Serverless technologies.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"c25dea02447eef08ddb2affdbb171485","text":"Mechanical empathy","correct":false},{"id":"db3e408a0aa09a4e83bdace8a1e57fcc","text":"Deploy into multiple Regions to go global in minutes.","correct":true},{"id":"e891a453952de1898dde71f36801790a","text":"Use Serverless architectures.","correct":true},{"id":"56110ec02fe5d9a3ae8e5a69af838158","text":"Have your IT staff master all new technologies.","correct":false},{"id":"8c3a4b8048462b1877e2da598308fe3a","text":"Democratize advanced technologies.","correct":true}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false},{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true}]},{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true}]},{"id":"485886ee-d768-43eb-bf66-99dbf6ca890f","domain":"tech","question":"When might Auto Scaling be used?","explanation":"Auto Scaling monitors your applications and automatically adjusts capacity to maintain steady, predictable performance at the lowest possible cost.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"294a68b8b2e864aff39edf8b7b5ae662","text":"Where predictable workload patterns exist","correct":false},{"id":"81a09fc79a5b8e06c0ba313f0c38b98f","text":"To provision resources that can be adjusted once per 24 hour period","correct":false},{"id":"653f92bb6e8a7e984815d88099db9ab2","text":"To control provisioning of S3 bucket capacity","correct":false},{"id":"4576fb5ff37cef52dcd4b0610521a97c","text":"When you require scalable capacity to maintain service levels in your environment","correct":true}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"8r7r7n13-hvyw-63f9-gltg-21wwwmux0grq","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that will remain operational even in the event of a component failure?","explanation":"a fault-tolerant system will remain operational even in the event of a component failure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/designing-fault-tolerant-applications/","title":"Building Fault-Tolerant Applications in the AWS Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"7bf4251c070de07f503b12b9d341daea","text":"Fault-tolerant","correct":true}]},{"id":"5l7vjhuv-wf9j-de1i-9aj4-e9dlg8u6cc76","domain":"billing","question":"Your Development team uses four on-demand EC2 instances, and your QA team has 5 reserved instances, only three of which are being used. Assuming all AWS accounts are under a single AWS Organization, how will the Development team's instances be billed?","explanation":"Assuming all instances are in the same AWS Organization, the reserved instance pricing for the unused QA instances will be applied to two of the four Dev instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"ecadbc09799c3807dfed5bd9ee9c6159","text":"All the Dev team's instances will be billed at the on-demand rate.","correct":false},{"id":"a6d19cc18b59af08baaa0f8247fca355","text":"The Dev team will be billed for two instances at on-demand prices and two instances at the reserved instance price.","correct":true},{"id":"b04b07a9c68b5b505f53afccb5616743","text":"The pricing for the reserved instances will shift from QA to Dev.","correct":false},{"id":"3ea9a50157f205cce00d0db169117711","text":"All the Dev instances will be billed at the reserved instance rate.","correct":false}]},{"id":"ff53359b-3559-40fd-9210-608f87ed6a5f","domain":"security","question":"Broadly speaking as a customer of AWS you responsible for:","explanation":"Generally speaking, as a customer of AWS you responsible for the security IN the cloud - meaning that you are responsible for the data, consumption and in-account configuration of AWS services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"2ac2679f0084e375060c216fe7477ab4","text":"Security OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2245b1bb4da8871fd09d4b5b6c52555e","text":"Security IN the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"e5a10169b294451720bbfc8cee548381","text":"Security both IN and OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"597b531cfe7d260c96c8ec4c4d4365ba","text":"None of security - AWS will manage all security for you","correct":false}]},{"id":"g817t8h6-2yd3-mhf7-wf2v-n82br09qszt7","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance certifications attests to the security of the AWS platform regarding credit card transactions?","explanation":"PCI DSS is a compliance program which must be followed by any organizations handling Credit Card data. AWS has achieved a PCI Level 1 certification, the highest level available","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"7829c763646fba446ea5831ef095f756","text":"ISO 27001","correct":false},{"id":"faf72a9a0f8e7e240ee1346d6e2056e3","text":"SOC 1","correct":false},{"id":"7aa6bd3f5ca63135c1f75edd80d7a6ba","text":"SOC 2","correct":false},{"id":"74073bf9c7bfe155fe513fd4624ae2f2","text":"PCI DSS Level 1","correct":true}]},{"id":"ism9fl1z-nho7-nn22-5sn8-4qqdyyu4pyeq","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWSâ€™ event-driven, serverless compute service?","explanation":"Lambda is AWSâ€™ event-driven, serverless compute service that allows you to run code without having to deploy or manage any of the underlying resources such as EC2 instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false}]},{"id":"czniv95k-ni5r-uuf9-ndk0-hf5pnoza8yy9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is a fast, fully managed data warehouse that makes it simple and cost-effective to analyze all your data using standard SQL and your existing Business Intelligence tools.","explanation":"Redshift is AWS' fully-managed data warehouse solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/","title":"About Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"594025cae6dfa6b9073dc25de93ddb56","text":"Kinesis","correct":false},{"id":"22ab04a992dc8483216fed8f9b932b77","text":"Elastic Map Reduce","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"b17c7706-de93-4fa7-9979-6704209afb8c","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support pricing plans provides a Technical Account Manager for proactive guidance on your AWS account?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides a designated Technical Account Manager (TAM) for your AWS account.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"3617c0aa-2fa9-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"For enhanced technical support, some AWS Support plans enable you to have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases. Which of the following choices offer this feature?","explanation":"With either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you can provide have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"382b7116-1f69-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum number of IAM users you can add to an AWS account at the same time?","explanation":"You can add up to 10 users at one time at the IAM console.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_users_create.html","title":"Creating an IAM User in Your AWS Account"}],"answers":[{"id":"98f13708210194c475687be6106a3b84","text":"20","correct":false},{"id":"e4da3b7fbbce2345d7772b0674a318d5","text":"5","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":true},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false},{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true},{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false},{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true}]},{"id":"3lwo2qi6-7yzt-o86p-u1vg-vxwsbedkzwt0","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the Security Pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?","explanation":"IAM, Detective Controls and Infrastructure Protection are key parts of the Security Pillar of the Well Archtiected Framwork. IAM - ensuring that only authorized and authenticated users are able to access your resources. Detective Controls to identify a potential security threat or incident. Infrastructure Protection covers the control methodologies, such as defense in depth, necessary to meet best practices and organizational or regulatory obligations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/architecture/well-architected/","title":"The Well-Architected FRamework"}],"answers":[{"id":"b9237ed805ea2fe23003f7e73fc1f7d4","text":"Detective Controls","correct":true},{"id":"d5552e0564007d93ff5937a9cb3bc491","text":"Customer Service","correct":false},{"id":"a571cb3f6a39b87e03d60bce4e086f6c","text":"Technical Account Management","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"96c4db3cd9b4be5b89474dff6d0fe9b1","text":"Infrastructure protection","correct":true}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"cfea2363-9af8-4536-b812-8ea53c44b11b","domain":"security","question":"You just had a Data Analyst join the company, and you have been tasked with creating a new IAM user accordingly. Although the user has received all the necessary credentials, she realized that she cannot perform any Amazon RDS actions on the Clients table. Which of the following are possible solutions to this issue?","explanation":"By default, an IAM user canâ€™t access anything in the AWS account. So, the inability to perform the RDS actions on the Clients table is not a technical or password issue. To grant the permission to do so, you would need to create an identity-based policy. However, if there is a group in the account with the permission policy that will grant such access, you can add the user to that group instead.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_access-management.html","title":"Overview of Access Management: Permissions and Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"1971cb80efb016ad4254e3847a847434","text":"Supply the password necessary to log into the AWS console.","correct":false},{"id":"94412f8679d11dc0613f571ca4fba16b","text":"Add the user to the group that has the necessary permissions policy.","correct":true},{"id":"7731c1bfd28c89eee71012d973fa5407","text":"Double-check the credentials you sent to the user.","correct":false},{"id":"2f96bead1d7909e64836767c4e098acd","text":"Create an identity-based policy.","correct":true},{"id":"f46d75eb223838121ca6bec9ca08eaaa","text":"Create a ticket for the Help Desk to resolve the issue.","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false}]},{"id":"6rxg9wr0-2vdy-xb2h-ds26-ul6n2c6g8bnu","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans feature access to AWS support via email only during business hours?","explanation":"The Developer support plan features access to AWS support during business hours via email. Business and Enterprise support plans allow 24x7 email support. The Basic support plan includes no email support options. Because the question specifies support *only* during business hours, there is only one correct answer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false}]},{"id":"q5ccmbtu-zf5i-qq17-r1r1-on26zatnbrbd","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are classified as Migration services?","explanation":"AWS Config and AWS OpsWorks are considered Management Tools, whereas Snowball (which helps you migrate massive amounts of data into cloud) and AWS Application Discovery Service (which helps you gather information about your on-premise environment) are considered Migration tools.  ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloud-migration/","title":"Migrating to AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"d2812559e560cb55cf64e189083ddbe7","text":"AWS OpsWorks","correct":false},{"id":"b59a3e47d727cea4324d91b7c8b07c2e","text":"AWS Application Discovery Service","correct":true},{"id":"c2d838ea2b9043be2161255da328dc60","text":"AWS Snowball","correct":true},{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":false}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, thereâ€™s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"55632ec1-3922-4d04-80c0-ff9b5b21c2d2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are AWS EC2 reserved pricing types?","explanation":"Reserved instances have three main pricing models, Standard, Convertible and Scheduled. Each model is targeted with a specific use case and benefits from its own level of discounted price","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"c9e63a71aa24afcde5e964d2530e2524","text":"Compute Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"bd1ad3385adf098b2e87d2bb75d87e39","text":"Scalable Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"e507a844b940fd588a1cbb5bb46fd4fe","text":"Standard Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"fe501a6493589e0d87e90fd0b4361e6f","text":"Convertable Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"c81edad1f6d23ac52025cde1cf22ba7b","text":"Scheduled Reserved Instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"ot1uc3t1-d222-o5zj-vont-qso51339d9ek","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services allows you to run complex analytic queries against petabytes of structured data, using sophisticated query optimization, columnar storage on high-performance local disks, and massively parallel query execution.","explanation":"Redshift allows you to run complex analytic queries against petabytes of structured data, using sophisticated query optimization, columnar storage on high-performance local disks, and massively parallel query execution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/","title":"About Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"594025cae6dfa6b9073dc25de93ddb56","text":"Kinesis","correct":false},{"id":"8d4c0b2cef256d21ab680366c8b1c6bf","text":"EMR","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"03ec629e-2f3a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following includes components such as AWS Cost Explorer and AWS Budgets?","explanation":"AWS Cost Management consolidates tools that help you access, organize, understand, control, and optimize costs and usage in the cloud. These tools include Cost Explorer for visualizing and analyzing your expenses. They also include Budgets for creating budgets and getting automatic alerts when your costs or usage exceed or are expected to exceed the set thresholds.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/aws-cost-management/","title":"AWS Cost Management"}],"answers":[{"id":"c92b59d331719f616526d493633f5f74","text":"End User Computing","correct":false},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false},{"id":"4e0c7fb2fac186d1b3b5afd0fe2c278a","text":"Cost Management","correct":true},{"id":"5525aee13c9e8a25b1f35514f33ab825","text":"Security, Identity, and Compliance","correct":false}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWSâ€™s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false},{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true},{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false},{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"ij3guy5r-65pf-5sad-nyrn-vkpusbdxd3cz","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can assist you with cost optimization?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor can assist you with the cost optimization of your AWS environment.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false}]},{"id":"5a9b87ae-3552-46ad-9cee-605c6dc2d534","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services can be used to create billing alarms?","explanation":"The CloudWatch service is used to create billing alarms. The Cost Explorer service is used to creates custom reports that facilitate the understanding of the organization's costs and data usage. Macie is a service used to identify sensitive data such as personally identifiable information (PII) stored in S3. The Athena service analyzes data using SQL queries stored in S3.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html","title":"Creating a Billing Alarm to Monitor Your Estimated AWS Charges"}],"answers":[{"id":"619ed6d20397878e9706fe9fa7c44579","text":"Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"582ca45acfd3e21caca8b786c1413850","text":"Athena","correct":false},{"id":"689485d385032d81c9cc43cbc981549a","text":"Macie","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":true}]},{"id":"918c058b-8c3d-4858-aa1b-de986b3379af","domain":"security","question":"Which following statement is true of newly created security groups with their default rules?","explanation":"By default, new security groups start with only an outbound rule to allow all traffic to leave the instances. You must add rules to enable any inbound traffic.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/VPC_SecurityGroups.html","title":"Security Groups for Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"d00cd55aa36c87aedb13b4c0829aa462","text":"New security groups block both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"8fbe4c39dc7d852a0b8aaa5b889b1ff1","text":"New security groups block outbound traffic and allow all incoming traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"66152806bd7636ccc1a33303917cdddd","text":"New security groups allow only outbound traffic and block all incoming traffic.","correct":true},{"id":"d21ab4dffc222de4dfe6fddddca20b1f","text":"New security groups allow both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false}]},{"id":"e64254c2-1a50-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services, which includes Amazon VPC. By comparison, the customer is responsible for what goes in the AWS Cloud. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses), security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic), and network ACLs as additional layers of security.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3ca98dadd6a9bcbe75450331cd449df5","text":"Network access control lists (network ACLs)","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"97fd1873341a4d886cd8a23614cef0ff","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Service","correct":false},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"dln2owy5-ju7b-em4o-t3bo-ry23tbt3vrfy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes Availability Zones?","explanation":"Availability Zones are distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures. Each Region is made up of one or more AZs. Availability Zones host almost every AWS service, including EC2 instances, S3 buckets, and much more. Some services will maintain copies of your data between Availability Zones, but this is dependent on the individual service (for example, S3 can store data in multiple AZ's, where an EC2 instance is tied to a single AZ). AWS's Content Distribution Network (CDN) is known as CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c6c3ae50e5264fd89c1ea0bb3c10e963","text":"Restricted areas designed specifically for the creation of Virtual Private Clouds.","correct":false},{"id":"5b3edf7c62ba2925e93886b2fed63697","text":"Two zones containing compute resources that are designed to automatically maintain synchronized copies of each other's data.","correct":false},{"id":"5c9e81d4612f9e8cb24d82a6015586c5","text":"Distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures.","correct":true},{"id":"172cd3aac7dce24131bdafec9988a618","text":"A Content Distribution Network used to deliver content to users","correct":false}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false},{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"6c02ad88-1feb-11ea-a32c-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon DynamoDB storage will you get?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 25 GB of DynamoDB storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"272aa49fa956677af70625391009423f","text":"25 GB","correct":true},{"id":"dcfebc6fbca2c5316f55c914e6593d2d","text":"100 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false}]},{"id":"2o4xzter-rc6s-wz14-cd0x-5ymcmahyoj0q","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an EC2 instance on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, EC2 patching is a Shared Control - AWS is responsible for the underlying hardware, but you as the user is responsible for patching the OS and Applications running in your instance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"92d4ae83f773c1e79ec7ae29b20fa481","text":"Patching the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"b8a5da87a2cdeca59f9782e25182f574","text":"Patching the applications","correct":true},{"id":"ce74e3a1c22bccb58acc0062f43153bd","text":"Patching the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3e164c265c82649647e641e322d93aa7","text":"Patching the operating system","correct":true}]},{"id":"4f5e27aa-65cf-46da-9db4-42b569eb0d05","domain":"tech","question":"Your employer, a major digital media company, needs you to implement an AWS service that delivers its dynamic web content worldwide, relying on edge locations to improve latency. Which one of the following services should you pick to accomplish that?","explanation":"CloudWatch monitors AWS resources and applications, CloudTrail increases visibility into user and resource activity, and there is no AWS service named CloudConnect. It is CloudFront that functions as Amazonâ€™s content delivery network, which is a system of distributed servers for delivering web content to users.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"Amazon CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"e45b2ed303bc7e3b63b82e4766fd7d8b","text":"CloudConnect","correct":false}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false},{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false}]}]}}}}
